templates.com 2019-04-08

# Templates.com Privacy Policy - Templates

Templates.com has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of the users of our website.  
Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy, and how we treat personally identifiable information collected from our visitors and users.

**GDPR Compliance**

Data protection is of the utmost importance to the team of Templates.com. 

Processing your personal data, including name, address, email, and/or phone number will always be in line with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), and in accordance with other data protection regulations applicable to Templates.com.

We have implemented every technical and organizational measure to ensure complete protection of our visitors’ personal data throughout the website. 

Since Internet-based data transmissions may have security gaps, absolute protection is not guaranteed. This is why each data subject can transfer personal data to us via all available means, e.g. by email or phone.

Controller for the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) is:  
JETIMPEX, INC.  
915 SE 2 Court,  
Fort Lauderdale,  
FL 33301  
United States  
TAX ID: 42-1774657

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**

This privacy policy covers Templates.com’s treatment of personally identifiable information collected by Templates.com through a website owned and operated by Templates.com.

This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Templates.com does not own or control, or of persons that Templates.com does not employ or manage, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which Templates.com website link.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

You can visit the website of Templates.com without revealing any personal information. However, Templates.com needs certain personal information if you wish to purchase our products, receive Templates.com newsletter, or use certain Templates.com services.

Where required, this information may include your personal contact information and/or your company contact information. Templates.com will use this information to reply to your inquiries, to provide you with requested products and services, to set up your member’s account, and to contact you regarding new products and services.

By accessing the services of Templates.com and voluntarily providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

**Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information**

Templates.com automatically receives and records non-personal information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested. Templates.com may use this information to customize the advertising and content you see and to fulfill your requests for certain products and services. However, Templates.com does not connect this non-personal data to any personal information collected from you.

Templates.com also allows third party companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Again, these cookies are not connected to any personal information. Third party cookie usage is subject to their own privacy policies, and Templates.com assumes no responsibility or liability for this usage.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Templates.com may disclose your personal information to third parties who work on behalf of Templates.com to provide products and services requested by you. We will share personal information for these purposes only with third parties whose privacy policies are consistent with ours or who agree to abide by our policies with respect to personal information.

Templates.com may otherwise disclose your personal information when:

  * We have your express consent to share the information for a specified purpose;
  * We need to respond to subpoenas, court orders or such other legal process;
  * We need to protect the personal safety of the users of our websites or defend the rights or property of Templates.com;
  * We find that your actions on our websites violate the Templates.com Terms of Use document or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.

**Consent**

If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this policy, please do not provide any personal information to Templates.com. If you have provided personal information to Templates.com and no longer consent to its use or disclosure as outlined herein, please notify Templates.com at privacy@templates.com.

**Security**

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. However, your Templates.com Information protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas of our websites, as identified on the site, Templates.com uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

We also safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access, through access control procedures, network firewalls and physical security measures.

Further, Templates.com retains your personal information only as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes identified above or as required by law.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Templates.com may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of Templates.com websites after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.

**Questions or Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or your own personal information, please contact us via the [contact form](https://www.templates.com/pages/info/contact-us.html).
